=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 17=
= الحلقة 17 =
Zeliu,
زيليو ،
Ms. Sun,
السيدة صن ،
I'm going vegan this year.
سأذهب نباتي هذا العام.
I can't stand looking at meat dishes as well.
لا أستطيع الوقوف عند النظر إلى أطباق اللحوم أيضًا.
It's okay.
حسنا.
I'll go vegan with you.
سأذهب معك نباتيًا.
Thanks, honey.
شكرا جميلتي.
What about you, Ms. Sun?
ماذا عنك يا سيدة صن؟
I'm fine too.
انا بخير ايضا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
(How pretentious.)
(يا له من ادعاء.)
Miss Liang is pretty and kind.
الآنسة ليانغ جميلة ولطيفة.
Mr. Bai is such a lucky man.
السيد باي رجل محظوظ.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
what's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
Do you not like the dishes?
ألا تحب الأطباق؟
The dishes are quite bland.
الأطباق لطيفة جدا.
I guess
اعتقد
you like to eat spicy
تحب أن تأكل حار
or greasy food.
أو طعام دهني.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Of course, I know.
بالطبع أنا أعلم.
I've studied health and beauty therapy.
لقد درست علاج الصحة والجمال.
Look at your nasal tip.
انظر إلى طرف أنفك.
There are clogged pores everywhere.
هناك مسام مسدودة في كل مكان.
I guess you don't really have a diet plan.
أعتقد أنه ليس لديك حقاً خطة حمية.
Listen,
استمع،
as a woman,
كإمرأة،
you should keep your skin clear and your body in shape.
يجب أن تحافظ على بشرتك صافية وجسمك في حالة جيدة.
That's how you get a perfect lover.
هكذا تحصل على عاشق مثالي.
Honey,
عسل،
am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Liang Wanqing,
ليانغ وانكينغ ،
don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا.
It won't work if I don't go this far.
لن ينجح الأمر إذا لم أذهب إلى هذا الحد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Trust me.
صدقني.
Babe,
فاتنة ،
it's hard to meet someone
من الصعب مقابلة شخص ما
as disciplined and perfect as you.
منضبطة ومثالية مثلك.
Come on.
هيا.
What will those ordinary women think
ماذا ستفكر هؤلاء النساء العاديات
if you praise me so highly?
إذا كنت تمدحني بشدة؟
There is only
هناك فقط
Miss Sun here.
الآنسة صن هنا.
Miss Sun, please don't mind me.
آنسة صن ، من فضلك لا تهتم بي.
You don't think I'm implying it's you, right?
أنت لا تعتقد أنني أعني أنه أنت ، أليس كذلك؟
Not at all.
لا على الاطلاق.
I'm a rather sloppy person.
أنا شخص قذر إلى حد ما.
Unlike Miss Liang, she's a gorgeous lady.
على عكس الآنسة ليانغ ، إنها سيدة رائعة.
But I think
لكنني أعتقد
everyone has their way of living.
كل شخص لديه طريقة معيشته.
As long as they are happy with their life.
طالما أنهم سعداء بحياتهم.
Just like Wang Xifeng in the Dream of the Red Chamber.
تمامًا مثل Wang Xifeng في حلم الغرفة الحمراء.
She may look glamorous on the surface,
قد تبدو براقة على السطح ،
but she pretends to be strong
لكنها تتظاهر بأنها قوية
to be capable, and to have a harmonious life.
أن تكون قادرًا وأن تعيش حياة متناغمة.
However, her husband cheated on her.
ومع ذلك ، فقد خانها زوجها.
She isn't happy at all.
هي ليست سعيدة على الإطلاق.
So what for?
إذن ماذا؟
I'm not Jia Lian.
أنا لست جيا ليان.
I'm just giving an example.
أنا فقط أعطي مثالا.
This isn't an appropriate example.
هذا ليس مثالا مناسبا.
Why would you think I'm talking about you, Mr. Bai?
لماذا تعتقد أنني أتحدث عنك يا سيد باي؟
(The Dream of the Red Chamber?)
(حلم الغرفة الحمراء؟)
(I've never read that.)
(لم أقرأ ذلك قط.)
(Judging from how ignorant Liang Wanqing is,)
(انطلاقا من مدى جهل ليانغ وانكينغ ،)
(I guess she's not educated.)
(أعتقد أنها ليست متعلمة).
(And she thinks)
(وهي تعتقد)
(she can win against Sun Weiyi?)
(يمكنها الفوز على سون ويي؟)
Ms. Sun,
السيدة صن ،
why don't you tell us about the concept of the online product's
لماذا لا تخبرنا عن مفهوم المنتجات عبر الإنترنت
advertising and packaging?
الإعلان والتعبئة والتغليف؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
There will be three different styles
سيكون هناك ثلاثة أنماط مختلفة
for the packaging of our products:
لتغليف منتجاتنا:
A mature and elegant style,
أسلوب ناضج وأنيق ،
a romantic and innocent style,
بأسلوب رومانسي وبريء ،
and a cool and modern style.
وأسلوب رائع وحديث.
Of these three styles,
من هذه الأنماط الثلاثة ،
we'll further divide them into bold and dramatic,
سنقسمهم إلى مزيد من الجرأة والدرامية ،
retro Hong Kong, China style, modern mean girl,
الرجعية هونغ كونغ ، النمط الصيني ، الفتاة المتوسطة الحديثة ،
cool and arrogant, feminine and seductive,
رائع ومتعجرف ، أنثوي ومغري ،
gentle and lazy, sweet and sexy.
لطيف و كسول و حلو و مثير.
A variety of cosmetics
مجموعة متنوعة من مستحضرات التجميل
will meet women's needs
ستلبي احتياجات المرأة
for makeup in the market.
للماكياج في السوق.
(Q,)
(س)
(get me a handsome man)
(أحضر لي رجل وسيم)
(to pretend to be my pursuer now.)
(لأتظاهر بأنني مطاردتي الآن).
(I'm at HB restaurant.)
(أنا في مطعم HB.)
(What happened?)
(ماذا حدث؟)
(I'll tell you later.)
(سأخبرك لاحقا.)
(As soon as possible.)
(في أقرب وقت ممكن.)
(On it!)
(عليه!)
Mr. Bai,
السيد باي ،
that's our concept for the product.
هذا هو مفهومنا للمنتج.
Great.
رائعة.
Look, there's a handsome man.
انظر ، هناك رجل وسيم.
That one.
هذا.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
why didn't you answer my call?
لماذا لم ترد على مكالمتي
Didn't you say you are going to eat with me?
ألم تقل أنك ستأكل معي؟
Sorry,
آسف،
I'm caught up with work.
أنا عالق في العمل.
Look at you, why are you wearing so little?
انظر إليك ، لماذا ترتدي القليل جدًا؟
What if you catch a cold?
ماذا لو أصبت بنزلة برد؟
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
he is...?
هو...؟
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
I'm pursuing Sun Weiyi.
أنا أطارد صن ويي.
She's a great woman,
إنها امرأة عظيمة
and she wouldn't fall for me.
ولن تقع في حضوري.
She finally agreed to have a meal with me today,
وافقت أخيرًا على تناول وجبة معي اليوم ،
but she stood me up.
لكنها وقفت لي.
So I had to come to find her.
لذلك كان علي أن آتي لأجدها.
I see.
أرى.
So now, can I have her back?
حتى الآن ، هل يمكنني استعادتها؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
We're done here.
نحن القيام به هنا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Really?
هل حقا؟
I'm so lucky today.
أنا محظوظ جدا اليوم.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
I want you to know
أريدك أن تعلم
that I'll always make time for you
سأخصص لك الوقت دائمًا
wherever, whenever.
أينما ومتى.
Mr. Bai,
السيد باي ،
it seems like she's not into you at all.
يبدو أنها ليست لك على الإطلاق.